<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cédric Gouy-Pailler | Projet REDEEM</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4321/fr/author/cedric-gouy-pailler/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:4321/fr/author/cedric-gouy-pailler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Cédric Gouy-Pailler</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>fr-FR</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:4321/fr/author/cedric-gouy-pailler/avatar_hu_9088b1b36ba4948e.png</url>
      <title>Cédric Gouy-Pailler</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/fr/author/cedric-gouy-pailler/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cédric Gouy-Pailler</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/fr/author/cedric-gouy-pailler/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/fr/author/cedric-gouy-pailler/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cédric Gouy-Pailler holds an engineering degree in electronics and signal processing from PHELMA (ex-ENSERG), Grenoble-INP, he received a doctorate in signal processing in 2009 at GIPSA-lab (Grenoble INP). Senior Expert at CEA since 2021, he is now leading the Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning laboratory at CEA LIST. He is working on innovative machine learning algorithms, with the objective of developing robust AI in adversarial contexts, and compatible with high privacy standards, through the use of homomorphic encryption and differential privacy. Cédric Gouy-Pailler has been involved in various National and European projects, involving both academic and industrials partners. He has been technical CEA leader (eCo-fev, EU project, 2012-2015), Work Package leader (STARLIGHT, EU project, 2021-2025, involving 52 partners), and project coordinator (StreamOPS, national 3 partners, 2018-2021 ; KINAITICS, EU project, 7 partners, 2022-2025).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us at AI Action Summit 6-7/02/2025 at Ecole Polytechnique, Institut Polytechnique de Paris</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4321/fr/post/06-02-25_aiactionsummit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:4321/fr/post/06-02-25_aiactionsummit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conference AI, Science, and Society&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are excited to share that the &lt;strong&gt;REDEEM project&lt;/strong&gt; will be actively represented at the upcoming &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://aiconference.ip-paris.fr/program/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;AI Conference 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; at IP Paris!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;session-on-trustworthy-ai&#34;&gt;Session on Trustworthy AI&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aymeric Dieuleveut&lt;/strong&gt; will contribute to the discussion on &lt;strong&gt;trustworthy AI&lt;/strong&gt;, providing insights into the latest advancements in secure and reliable AI systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;poster-session&#34;&gt;Poster Session&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Batiste Le Bars&lt;/strong&gt; (INRIA) will present his work on &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;Improved Stability and Generalization Guarantees of the Decentralized SGD Algorithm.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This research challenges prior claims on decentralized learning, demonstrating that decentralized stochastic gradient descent (SGD) can match centralized approaches in generalization while benefiting from communication-aware optimizations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://aiconference.ip-paris.fr/program/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;AI Conference 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to engage with cutting-edge research in AI, federated learning, and decentralized optimization!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
